拜托  就今晚这一次  别谈论任何不好的事情
Please, tonight for once, I don't want anything bad talked about.
好好享用这一餐
Enjoy your meal.
好  那么我来说件有趣的事
fine,Then I'll tell you something funny.
你们知道罗席嘉先生吗
You know who I mean by Dr. Raszeja?
-那位军医?  -对 军医
- The surgeon? - The surgeon.
别问我为什么  但因为某个原因
for some reason and not ask me why
德国人允许他到犹太人区做手术
The Germans allowed him into the ghetto to perform an operation.
对犹太人动刀?
On a Jew?
他们让波兰人为犹太人开刀?
They let a Pole to come in to operate on a Jew?
他拿到了通行证  我就知道这些
He got a pass, that's all I know. Anyway, so...
他让病人昏睡过去然后开始动手术
he puts the patient to sleep and starts the operation.
他才刚划下第一刀  SS部队就闯进来
He'd just made the first incision when the SS burst in...